

PROFILE-

Senior student at the Higher Institute of Engineering and Technology KFS, with experience in web development, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++, desktop development with C#, the basics of SQL Server DBMS, the basics of Data Structures with C++, OOP with C#, and basics of networking.

CONTACT-

PHONE

+201140855227

Mail

Most.saleh@hotmail.com

Address

Tanta, Egypt

SOCIAL MEDIA

WEBSITE

Eng-mostafasaleh.blogspot.com

LinkedIn

Linkedin.com/in/mostafasaleh5

Mostafa Saleh

Software Engineer

EXPERIENCE

Jul 2021-Aug 2021

INTERN @ WF

I was a trainee at Telecom Egypt Miami Exchange in Alexandria, Egypt. I learned about Introduction to Optical fibre cables, Introduction to "FTTH" networks, introduction to traffic devices such as PCM, WDH, SDH and WDM.

Aug 2021-Oct 2021

SCHOLARSHIP HOLDER @ EGFWD

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.JS and the DOM.

Nov 2022-Oct 2022

PATHOLOGICAL PHENOMENA FOR BROILERS PROJECT @ AIOT

I worked on the dataset to train a model to recognize sick broilers using deep learning and computer vision. The Al detects broilers and track them and differentiates among sick and healthy broilers.

EDUCATION

Sep 2018-Jul 2023

4TH YEAR, SENIOR STUDENT

STUDENT @ HIGHER INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY KFS

I'm a student in the fourth year Computer and Control engineering department.

SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP

Java

Java

WEB

WEB